<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<cards>
  <version>1.0.0</version>
  <!--  -->
  <card id="1" type="page-content">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Sales Consultant—New]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Connected Vehicles Services provides another way you can meet customers’ needs and build lasting relationships.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg1.png]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Sales Consultant—New]]></label>
        <popup>
          <popupContent><![CDATA[
            <p>Each dealership has its own sales process, but the general flow of the customer journey is the same, sold customer or not. Read "The 7 States of the Sales Cycle" to learn more about this general flow.</p>
            <p>Do you know how the sales process has been refined at your dealership? Take some time to talk to your colleagues and Sales Manager to find out. Download the workbook to document how the sales process is unique at your dealership.</p>]]></popupContent>
        </popup>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="2" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Sales Consultant—Pre-Owned]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Our pre-owned vehicles may be a customer’s first introduction into the brand. Be sure you’re laying the groundwork for everything we offer.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg2.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <!--<actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[true]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Test label ONE]]></label>
        <link>
          <link-url><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl]]></link-url>
        </link>
      </action>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[true]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Test label TWO]]></label>
        <link>
          <link-url><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl]]></link-url>
        </link>
      </action>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[true]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Test label THREE]]></label>
        <link>
          <link-url><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/?gws_rd=ssl]]></link-url>
        </link>
      </action>
    </actions>-->
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Sales Consultant—Pre-Owned]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
          <p>As a Sales Consultant of Used and Certified Pre-Owned (CPO) vehicles, Connected Vehicle Services offers you a selling edge in the flooded pre-owned market. Using the plans to identify what features and services matter most to customers can help you identify a make and model that might suit them best.</p>
          <p>The new plans add extra incentive to our excellent line of Certified vehicles. Many of these customers will be first-time buyers in our brand and may not know the exclusivity of these features and services.</p>
          <p>Lay the groundwork for a lifelong relationship with these customers. Do they want connectivity, or are they more interested in safety and security? Discuss the plans and their benefits. Find out what matters most, so when you hit the Blue Button, the customer and the advisor can easily identify the plan that serves the customer's needs, and the customer can enjoy the exclusive benefits of GM ownership.</p>]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="3" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Service Consultant]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Connected Vehicle Services plans aren’t just for the Sales floor. The Service Lane can provide you an opportunity to discuss the technology features our vehicles offer.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg3.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Service Consultant]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
          <p>As a Service Consultant, you know that standard maintenance and upkeep of our vehicles is paramount to maintaining GM’s standard of superior performance.</p>
          <p>As owners visit your Service Lane, you can discuss important maintenance details and notifications they can receive through our new Connected Vehicle Services plans. Lay the groundwork with your customers. Do they want connectivity, or are they more interested in safety and security?</p>
          <p>Let them know the advantages of maintenance notifications, on-demand diagnostics and vehicle alerts. These features can help them keep their vehicles in top condition and bring them back to you.</p>
          <p>Discuss the exclusive features of the OnStar Safety & Security plan. Customers may not always be able to reach your trusted Certified Technician, but their trusted Advisor is always there with the push of a button.</p>
          <p>And that knowledge increases the trust owners have in you and your department.</p>
        ]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>
  <!--  -->


  <!--  -->
  <card id="4" type="video">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[A New Approach]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Technology is changing the world, and our customers are changing with it. Watch the video to understand why GM is taking a new approach to Connected Vehicle Services. (<span class="bolded">Required</span>)]]></cardBlurb>
    <vidSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/video/1.mp4]]></vidSrc>
    <posterSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/img/vidPposter1.jpg]]></posterSrc>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/vidPposter1.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[true]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Video: A New Approach (Value Prop)]]></label>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="5" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Customer Benefits]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Customers are at the heart of our business, which is why we’ve taken a new approach to better meet their needs. Click to learn the benefits our new approach will have for them.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg5.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Customer Benefits]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
          <p>We continue to broaden our offerings so customers can bring their digital lives into their vehicles and stay connected and safe on the go.</p>
          <p>With Remote Access, vehicle diagnostics, Wi-Fi, in-vehicle apps and smart alerts, GM offers one of the industry’s widest range of connected vehicle experiences along with the safety and security of the OnStar brand.</p>
          <p>Some customers want connectivity while others want safety and security. Separating these services gives customers more choice and enables customers to pay only for what they want.</p>
          <p>We offer a Trial Period for customers to test the options and incentives for on-the-spot auto-renewal.</p>
          ]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="6" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Sales Consultant Benefits]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Connected Vehicle Services is another way for you to build lasting relationships with your customers. Click to learn the benefits our new approach will have for you.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg6.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Sales Consultant Benefits]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
          <p>A trial activation for OnStar during the Blue Button Welcome Call is a required component for Sales Consultants to be eligible for their SFE incentives.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>Online Enrollment</li>
            <li>One-Click Enrollment</li>
            <li>Owner Center Registration</li>
            <li>Blue Button Welcome Call</li>
          </ul>
          <p>The added benefits of this new approach give our customers flexibility and an array of options to better meet their technology needs, which in turn improves their relationship with their vehicle, our brands and your dealership.</p>]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="7" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Service Consultant Benefits]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[In the Service Lane, trust is key. Connected Vehicle Services offers another way to build that trust. Click to learn the benefits our new approach will have for you.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg7.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Service Consultant Benefits]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
          <p>Customers may arrive in the Service Lane with an inactive plan. Most 2011 and newer vehicles qualify for Connected Access at no charge to provide helpful features such as vehicle diagnostics, Smart Driver, and Marketplace.</p>
          <p>You can discuss the plans with these customers and provide service and peace of mind for them, along with repeat service lane visits.</p>
          <p>The added benefits of this new approach to our plans give our customers flexibility and an array of options to better meet their technology needs, which in turn improves their relationship with their vehicle, our brands and your dealership.</p>
          <p>In addition, there are EarnPower Activation Incentives for each vehicle activation.</p>
          ]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>
  <!--  -->

  <!--  -->
  <card id="8" type="video">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[New Plan Details]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[More focused and catered to meet the needs of our modern customers, the new Connected Vehicle Services plans will help customers make the most of their vehicle experience. (<span class="bolded">Required</span>)]]></cardBlurb>
    <vidSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/video/2.mp4]]></vidSrc>
    <posterSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/img/vidPposter2.jpg]]></posterSrc>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/vidPposter2.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[true]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Video: New Plan Details (Plan)]]></label>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="9" type="links">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[New vs. Old]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Click to take a quick look at how our new plans compare to the old ones, and the changes we've made to make them more focused.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg8.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[FAQs]]></label>
        <link>
          <link-url><![CDATA[https://gm.connectsolutions.com/p179c5dn6wt/output/Printable_Plans.pdf?download=Printable_Plans.pdf]]></link-url>
        </link>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <!--<card id="9" type="popup">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[New vs. Old]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Click to take a quick look to see how our new plans compare to the old ones, and they changes we’ve made to make them more focused.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg8.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[New vs. Old]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[<div class="col-md-12 clearfix"><img class="img-responsive" src="resources/media/img/cardImg8.jpg" alt="New vs. Old"/></div>]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>-->

  <card id="10" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Welcome Call]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Lay the groundwork and let our OnStar Advisors do the rest. Click to learn how the Welcome Call will help customers meet their technology needs.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg9.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Welcome Call]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
          <p>The new Welcome Call is designed to get owners, new and old, into the Connected Vehicle Services plan that meets their needs and the experience they wish to have with their vehicle.</p>
          <ul>
            <li>Lay the groundwork by speaking to the customer about what services and features matter to them most. Are they interested in being connected to their vehicle, or are emergency services and safety more important to them? Do they like having a person on call at the push of a button to help them if the road gets rough?</li>
            <li>Once the customer has an idea of what they want, the OnStar Advisor can quickly and easily offer information on the plans that suit their desires.</li>
            <li>The Advisor will get them set up for the Trial Period and offer details on the plans that interest customers most.</li>
            <li>The OnStar Advisor will help set up the account and get the customer enrolled in a Monthly Service Plan that allows the customer to maximize their desired experience with their vehicle.</li>
            <li>The Sales or Service Consultant can stay in the vehicle to assist the customer and the Advisor through the process.</li>
          </ul>]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="11" type="video">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Trial Period—Buick, Chevrolet, GMC]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Click to watch a video on the new Trial Period changes for our auto industry-leading technology.]]></cardBlurb>
    <vidSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/video/3.mp4]]></vidSrc>
    <posterSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/img/vidPposter3.jpg]]></posterSrc>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/vidPposter3.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Trial Period—Buick, Chevrolet, GMC]]></label>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="12" type="video">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Trial Period—Cadillac]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Click to watch a video on the new Trial Period changes for our auto industry-leading technology.]]></cardBlurb>
    <vidSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/video/4.mp4]]></vidSrc>
    <posterSrc><![CDATA[resources/media/img/vidPposter4.jpg]]></posterSrc>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/vidPposter4.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Trial Period—Cadillac]]></label>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>
  <!--  -->


  <!--  -->
  <card id="13" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Online Enrollment]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Getting your customers enrolled in all our programs and resources will help them enjoy everything GM ownership has to offer. Click to learn how you can assist your customers.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg10.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Online Enrollment]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
        <p>In order to best serve your customer and to qualify for your SFE incentive for new vehicle sales, make sure the customer sets up their account via Online Enrollment.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Go over the Connected Vehicle Services plans and packages.</li>
          <li>Review the Multi-Year plan options.</li>
          <li>Discuss the new Confirmation Page with your customer so they know their enrollment is complete.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="14" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[New Owner Setup]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[Make sure your customers understand everything that comes with being a GM owner. Click to learn how to help them get going.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg11.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[New Owner Setup]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
        <p>It is key to make sure your customers complete the New Owner Onboarding setup.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Make sure the customer has created log in credentials and explain Owner Center to the customer.</li>
          <li>Check that the customer can log in properly to their brand mobile app.</li>
          <li>Encourage them to opt-in to the My GM Rewards program so all of their accounts can be linked at once.</li>
          <li>Completing this process also applies towards the new vehicles sales SFE incentive.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="15" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[OnStar Advisor]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[The OnStar Advisor will assist the customer in choosing the right plan. Click to learn how you can help make this call valuable for everyone involved.]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg12.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[OnStar Advisor]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[<p>Setting up the Blue Button Welcome Call will be the most important aspect of your role in the changes.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Lay the groundwork.</li>
          <li>Find out what is most important to your customer when it comes to their vehicle experience—connectivity or safety and security.</li>
          <li>Let the Advisor know what is important to the customer so the Advisor can review the correct information with them.</li>
          <li>Remember, you can stay in the vehicle during the call and assist the customer and the Advisor through the process.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>
  <!--  -->


  <!--  -->
  <card id="16" type="links">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Key Takeaways]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg13.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Key Takeaways]]></label>
        <link>
          <link-url><![CDATA[https://gm.connectsolutions.com/p75ppb7bcqz/output/TakeAway.pdf?download=TakeAway.pdf]]></link-url>
        </link>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="17" type="text">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Support Materials]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg11old.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Key Takeaways]]></label>
        <popupContent><![CDATA[
        <ul>
          <li>Access the Dealer In-Vehicle Technology Library via GM GlobalConnect to access support materials and reference materials for OnStar and Connected Vehicle Services.</li>
          <li><span class="bolded">STEP 1</span>: Log in with your dealer credentials.</li>
          <li><span class="bolded">STEP 2</span>: Click <span class="bolded">App Center</span>.</li>
          <li><span class="bolded">STEP 3</span>: Scroll down to find Dealer In-Vehicle Technology Library.</li>
          <li>Click <span class="italicized">Launch</span> to be redirected to the Library's website.</li>
          <li><span class="bolded italicized">Note</span>: <span class="italicized">After adding the site to My Shortcuts, you will be able to see it under Applications on the right hand side menu</span>.</li>
        </ul>
        ]]></popupContent>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="18" type="links">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Printable Plans]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg8.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[FAQs]]></label>
        <link>
          <link-url><![CDATA[https://gm.connectsolutions.com/p179c5dn6wt/output/Printable_Plans.pdf?download=Printable_Plans.pdf]]></link-url>
        </link>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>

  <card id="19" type="links">
    <cardHeading><![CDATA[Survey]]></cardHeading>
    <cardBlurb><![CDATA[]]></cardBlurb>
    <imgSrc><![CDATA[../resources/media/img/cardImg14.jpg]]></imgSrc>
    <actions>
      <action>
        <required><![CDATA[false]]></required>
        <label><![CDATA[Survey]]></label>
        <link>
          <link-url><![CDATA[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/HCLJJ6P]]></link-url>
        </link>
      </action>
    </actions>
  </card>
</cards>
